I like your little face, your special smile,
your lips, so juicy.
I want to taste them. You whisper in my ear
and start kissing me.
I'm filled with joy.
Ay, mamá, it's just too much.
Ay, mamá, I don't know what I'm going to do.
I can't resist your honey-tasting kisses.
As much as I don't want to.
I know I'm going to fall.
I like your little eyes and your womanly body.
I can't believe how pretty you look
you tell me you love me,
that we must get married.
I start thinking you're trying to trap me.
Ay, mamá, I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm going crazy for this amazing woman.
Because everyone wants her
just for the pleasure.
Ay, mamá, I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm going crazy for this amazing woman.
For this amazing woman. Ay, mamá.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Because everyone wants her
just for the pleasure.
Thank you. Cheers.
Thank you guys, it's an honor to be here.
Thank you guys so much for being here with
all our beautiful friends from Folkways.
Thank you guys for being here. And of course,
Daniel Sheehy. We love you, man. Laura...
This next song is an original
composition by Mr. Josh Baca here.
I sit here in the day, staring up
at the sun so high.
Wondering if I'm lucky enough
to be given your time.
Even though we met
just a few days before.
I learned so much about you,
I thirst to learn more.
I said a boom and a bang
and my heart pounds for you.
I sit here in the night, staring up
at the moon above.
I'm wondering if I'm lucky enough
to be given your love.
Baby, thinking about you.
You know you're really fine.
Wanna get to know you, darling.
Gonna make you mine.
I said a boom and a bang
and my heart pounds for you.
I sit here in the day, staring up
at the sun so high.
Wondering if I'm lucky enough
to be given your time.
Even though we met just a few days before.
Learned so much about you,
I thirst to learn more.
I said a boom and a bang
and my heart pounds for you.
Thank you.
Thank you guys so much.
All right. Next number we're doing is
an original song called "Herido."
And a special guest on the güiro,
Mr. Felix Contreras.
I love you because I love you,
I adore you with great passion.
I love you with great tenderness.
You left my heart wounded.
You left me, unfaithful woman.
You found a new love.
You forgot my eternal love.
You shattered a dream of two.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
I love you because I love you.
I adore you with great passion.
I love you with great tenderness.
You left my heart wounded.
You left me, unfaithful woman.
You found a new love and forgot my eternal love.
You shattered a dream of two.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
I remember the beautiful nights
when you gave me your love.
You left a hole in my soul,
wounded by a great pain.
Thank you.
Thank you, Felix. Very good.
All right. Saludos. Would like to say hello to
Worldhaus Records. Michael Hardie
and Myla Hardie.
All right.
Now, when you hear the daily news.
Try to sell you a case of the blues.
Human conditions makes you so sad.
Politicians make you so damn mad.
Déjalo, let it go.
Now when love let you down.
A night on the train,
leaving town.
Dragging your heart across the ground.
Searching for the lost
the lost and found.
Déjalo, let it go.
There's some people who'd pull you down,
pass your name
all over town. They only live to criticize.
They'd like to put other people down.
Déjalo, let it go.
If you feel bad for any reason.
Any day of any season.
you can sure that you still have hope
when you're down at the end of your rope.
Déjalo, let it go.
Thank you. Thank you.
I fell in love for the first time
under the moon when I kissed you.
The night was cold, you came close.
And with a sweet kiss, I fell in love with you.
You are as pretty as flowers.
And I adore you unconditionally.
Your eyes shine like stars.
You are my love. I love you so.
I fell in love for the first time
under the moon when I kissed you.
The night was cold, you came close.
And with a sweet kiss, I fell in love with you.
You are as pretty as flowers.
And I adore you unconditionally.
Your eyes shine like stars.
You are my love. I love you so.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you,
guys.